https://www.khaoscontrol.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy was last updated on 25/10/2019General Data Protection RegulationWe comply with the principles of GDPR when dealing with all data received from visitors to the site.Our ServicesWe only hold the data necessary to offer services provided on our website.Required PeriodWe only hold personal data for as long as is necessary. Once data is no longer needed it is deleted from our files.Data StorageFor administrative reasons data may be passed to and stored securely with third party service providers located outside the EEA (European Economic Area).Email UpdatesWe regularly email website news and information updates to those customers who have specifically subscribed to our email service. All subscription emails sent by us contain clear information on how to unsubscribe from our email service.Our PromiseWe never sell, rent or exchange mailing lists.Data Shared with PartnersWe may however share commercial and technical data with our partners where a customer has accessed and used our website via a site belonging to one of our partners. However, such information will also be subject to our partners’ privacy policies.Email OptionsIf you subscribe to our email service via a partner site, that partner may wish to send you details via email of other products and services, which may be of interest to you. However, when you subscribe directly to our email service you will be asked whether you wish to receive such emails.Partner Privacy PoliciesPlease note that we only share data with partners that operate their own privacy policy.SpamIn accordance with the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, we never send bulk unsolicited emails, (popularly known as Spam) to email addresses.Product UpdatesWe may send emails to existing customers or prospective customers who have enquired or registered with us, regarding products or services directly provided by us.Email ContentAll emails sent by us will be clearly marked as originating from us. All such emails will also include clear instructions on how unsubscribe from our email service and any future emails. Such instructions will either include a link to a page to unsubscribe or a valid email address to which you should reply, with “unsubscribe” as the email subject heading.Tracking Cookies Our website uses “cookies” to track use and allow customers to purchase from our website, specifically Google Analytics’ Demographics and Interests Reports. Please note that these cookies do not contain or pass any confidential or financial information or any other information that could be used to identify individual visitors or customers purchasing from our website. We use this information to better understand who is visiting our website to further enhance and improve the content we produce and the experience we provide. Processing PurposeWe will only process your data when we send you emails.Legal Basis for ProcessingYour agreement to these terms confirms means you are giving us consent to process your data.Your RightsYou have the right to access and alter data we have on you, the right to limit or stop our processing of that data, and also the right to request its deletion. We must comply with deletion, access and alteration requests within one month.
Complaints regarding any aspect of our treatment of your rights can be made to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).Contact UsIf you have any questions relating to our Privacy Policy please email us at sales@khaoscontrol.com or call 0845 25 75 111.Analytics & Advertising, and Pixel TechnologyGoogle Tag Manager is a piece of java script code we have incorporated into each of our web pages. This provides a series of functions for transmitting application-specific events and user-defined data to Facebook, Twitter. We use this data to record information about the way visitors use our website. Every Facebook and Twitter user has a unique, device-independent ID that allows us to address and recognize users for commercial purposes via Facebook and Twitter ads.
Want to receive more great content? Stay up to date with the latest eCommerce news and inspiration, as well as system updates. Check out our blog to see the type of content you can expect to receive.
Get a little Khaos in your inbox
SolutionsSalesQuotationsSales OrdersSales InvoicesReturns ManagementPayment ProcessingCustomer Price ListsPromotionsDashboardEcommerceEPOSSupply ChainSupplier ManagementPurchase Order SystemSupplier Price ListsReorder ToolsSupplier Performance TrackingDelivery NoteSupplier ReturnsConsignmentsSitesInventoryInventory Management SoftwarePacks and Bills of MaterialBarcode ScanningReturns ManagementBackorderingSize Colour StyleWarehousingHand Held TerminalsPickingPackingCourier ManagementLocationsBatchesPallet TrackingJob AllocationsCRMCustomer ManagementPipeline TrackingList SegmentationEmail ManagerClientsAccountingAccounts ManagementNominal AccountingBank ReconciliationTax RegisterReportsXero IntegrationSales and Purchase LedgerSolutions OverviewProductsKhaos Control CloudKhaos Control Cloud|A cloud based ERP solution to manage your businessOverviewIntegrationsProduct RoadmapPricingKhaos ControlKhaos Control |A complete solution for all your business management needsOverviewCase StudiesIntegrationsKhaos Control HybridKhaos Control Hybrid|Unleash the power of hybrid with all our products in one!OverviewProducts OverviewPartnersBlogSupportKhaos Control CloudSupport websiteKhaos ControlSupport websiteKhaos Control APIAPI DocumentationContact UsSign InKhaos Control CloudApplicationAdmin PortalKhaos ControlSupport PortalFREE DEMO
